* Individuals
* Businesses
* Features

Privacy Policy
==============

### We collect data necessary for automating your job application process

Your privacy is important to us. It is LoopCV LTD 's policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect from you across our website, https://www.loopcv.pro, and other sites we own and operate.  
  
We only ask for personal information when we truly need it to provide a service to you. We collect it by fair and lawful means, with your knowledge and consent. We also let you know why we’re collecting it and how it will be used.  
  
We only retain collected information for as long as necessary to provide you with your requested service. What data we store, we’ll protect within commercially acceptable means to prevent loss and theft, as well as unauthorised access, disclosure, copying, use or modification.  
  
We don’t share any personally identifying information publicly or without your consent, except when required to by law.  
  
We may share information to third-parties, when necessary to complete the job application process and provide a smooth experience.  
  
We use cookies, analytics, and other similar technologies that are needed to provide a smooth user experience, measure engagement, and improve our platform.  
  
Our website may link to external sites that are not operated by us. Please be aware that we have no control over the content and practices of these sites, and cannot accept responsibility or liability for their respective privacy policies.  
  
You are free to refuse our request for your personal information, with the understanding that we may be unable to provide you with some of your desired services.  
  
You can request to download your personal data we store or to delete your personal account on LoopCV, by contacting us at support@loopcv.com.  
  
Your continued use of our website will be regarded as acceptance of our practices around privacy and personal information. If you have any questions about how we handle user data and personal information, feel free to contact us.

Loopcv Helps You find a job faster
----------------------------------

Automate your job search today. Never miss an opportunity.

12 London Road, London, England gb

###### Features

###### Our clients

###### Company

###### Useful links

All rights reserved 2021 | LoopCV
